<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<horo>
<date yesterday="01/18/2022" today="01/19/2022" tomorrow="01/20/2022" tomorrow02="01/21/2022" />

<aries>
<yesterday>
Today, for complete happiness, you will lack only the approval of others. Try not to miss a single chance to get it. Don't be too stiff - snobbery is bad for your health.
</yesterday>
<today>
Gossip is such a delight. You have to be a completely unscrupulous hypocrite to say that you, they say, are not interested in them at all. Today you have a chance to gossip freely, for several years to come.
</today>
<tomorrow>
It is so difficult to remain patient, being on the verge of big and very important events for you. However, you have to, otherwise you risk preventing them from happening.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Today should be a good day for someone who has set as his goal the task of charming someone and completely capturing his thoughts and feelings. But be careful, you can do it unconsciously.
</tomorrow02>
</aries>

<taurus>
<yesterday>
Today, your appearance will be of particular importance. Let you tremble in your soul like a hare's tail - put on a mask of calm self-confidence, and no one will catch you by the hand.
</yesterday>
<today>
You may not have found the best way to show interest in someone, and this someone is in a state of mild amazement and does not understand at all what is wanted from him. Be simple.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Today you should visit some crowded and, preferably, not boring place. By spending this day in splendid isolation, you will deprive yourself and others of great entertainment.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Do not use raised tones of your voice today. Firstly, it is harmful to the vocal cords, and secondly, the person you are going to yell at does not deserve it at all.
</tomorrow02>
</taurus>

<gemini>
<yesterday>
Today you can allow yourself to relax, banish the feeling of distrust towards anyone and generally give up unpleasant thoughts. You'll catch up tomorrow.
</yesterday>
<today>
Today is worth spending in the company of good friends and the nth number of bottles of beer (where n depends on the size of the company). Creative activity will not be successful today.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Today you can afford to deviate somewhat from the generally accepted canons of behavior. Don't think too much about what it could turn out to be, just act.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Today you have every chance to get into a business or legal puddle. Ask as many questions as possible - an unexplained detail can do a disservice.
</tomorrow02>
</gemini>

<cancer>
<yesterday>
Where emotions reign, logic has no power. The spontaneity of someone's decisions today can really ruin your plans. Be careful when choosing the person you are going to rely on.
</yesterday>
<today>
Today it will be important not what you know, but how you got this knowledge. If you do not want to expand on this slippery topic, it is better to keep the indicated information to yourself.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Be careful in dealing with others. Too much depends on how it will be carried out today to allow yourself to accidentally offend a person, for example, by demonstrating your superiority.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
If you wish, today you could hear and understand the language of animals and plants. Your senses will be heightened and will have to be carefully guarded.
</tomorrow02>
</cancer>

<leo>
<yesterday>
Today, almost everything will go contrary to your expectations, not to mention desires. But you should not give up, by the evening it may turn out that it is even better.
</yesterday>
<today>
Today will be one of the most successful for you in recent times. Take advantage of this, for the Moon, which influences your destiny in such a positive way, will not remain in this position forever.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Today, when asking a question, do not expect too much of an answer. However, you yourself will now be distinguished by some indecision. Why demand anything else from others?
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Beware of overly expressive statements, especially with a pathetic tinge. However, this does not mean that every conversation should be controlled by an equalizer.
</tomorrow02>
</leo>

<virgo>
<yesterday>
You are standing at a fork, and everything would be fine, but you are not standing alone. And you will have to choose the road not only for yourself. Keep this in mind.
</yesterday>
<today>
You tend to complicate the situation, and you succeed with brilliance. But do you need this?
</today>
<tomorrow>
It's good to be able to do whatever you want, but for some reason it gets boring quickly. Channel your crazy energy into doing something that someone else wants.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Today, you may be exposed to a responsibility that you, in general, do not crave at all. Do not refuse immediately, just set your own conditions.
</tomorrow02>
</virgo>

<libra>
<yesterday>
This day is worth spending in the company of onewow, but very close to you person. It is possible that you will even feel a little sad, but this feeling will be rather pleasant.
</yesterday>
<today>
Today you may be challenged. Take it as if you do it daily, it will discourage the enemy.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Start moving, determine the direction later. If you don't care where you go, ask someone for advice and do the opposite.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Today you will be extremely touchy, and completely out of business. Try to either avoid communicating with others altogether, or treat their words more simply.
</tomorrow02>
</libra>

<scorpio>
<yesterday>
Your strength is growing. Today, everything will obey your word, oh something, perhaps, and look. Good day for telekinesis.
</yesterday>
<today>
Today you have a chance to acquire something very durable, perhaps for a lifetime. Take steps to ensure that this does not turn out to be a chronic runny nose, for example.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Today you will have to be patient. It is better to do it voluntarily, preferably with songs.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Having planned this day - do not change plans. It will be successful only if you follow the schedule point by point.
</tomorrow02>
</scorpio>

<sagittarius>
<yesterday>
You were somewhat sloppy and now you will have to exert all your strength to cope with the task assigned to you. It is quite possible, although not easy, henceforth be more careful when making promises.
</yesterday>
<today>
Your task is to take today and, as the great sculptor once recommended, cut off everything superfluous from it. The earlier in the morning you manage to plan it in this way, the more successful it will be.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Don't be afraid to communicate your feelings to the person you have them for (this goes for any kind of feeling). Today is the day to do it.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Today your optimism will be so strong that you will be able to handle almost anything. Having no fear of failure helps a lot in your work.
</tomorrow02>
</sagittarius>

<capricorn>
<yesterday>
Be prepared for sudden turns of fortune. Today you will have the opportunity to catch her by the tail. Perhaps some old things will have to be put aside in order to throw all the forces into the implementation of a fresh idea.
</yesterday>
<today>
You enjoy taking on a lot of responsibility. Although your labors will be hard, they will bring satisfaction, because you will have the strength to bring them to the end.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Today it will be difficult for you to calculate the strength, you may well break something. The situation can get out of your control - be as careful as possible.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
You tend to take too much personally. It’s not worth it, far from everything is done on purpose to offend you, something has nothing to do with you at all.
</tomorrow02>
</capricorn>

<aquarius>
<yesterday>
Today, the outside world will try in every possible way to rudely invade your privacy, thus ruining your mood for the whole day. Think about it, is it worth it to retire if you still won’t leave alone?
</yesterday>
<today>
You can respect someone else’s point of view as much as you like, but today it’s just better to stick to your own opinion and not give up positions.
</today>
<tomorrow>
That swamp that you've been stomping on up to now is becoming such a pretty rivulet with solid banks. Get out, dry yourself, otherwise suddenly there is a swamp ahead again?
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
By the end of today, some things may start to seem very strange to you. Be open to the perception of the new, there will be plenty of it today. And do not forget to thank the one who will open your eyes to this new one.
</tomorrow02>
</aquarius>

<pisces>
<yesterday>
Today, you may feel like a slave to your plans, which are made taking into account only one need, and not at all desires. You are suffering in vain, no one bothers you to make appropriate changes to your schedule.
</yesterday>
<today>
Today, the most difficult problem may be deciding on the choice of the color of the handkerchief. The rest shouldn't be a problem.
</today>
<tomorrow>
Today you can become a victim of apathy, perhaps for a long time. The best way to deal with it is prevention. Don't let yourself rest and she may not be able to get close to you.
</tomorrow>
<tomorrow02>
Don't say anything today that you're completely unsure of. Under no circumstances bet.
</tomorrow02>
</pisces>



</horo>